A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Legislative Files, 2002-2005
  - 12 VAC 30-120 DMAS, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - 12 VAC 30-120 DMAS, 2002-2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - 12 VAC 30-130 DMAS, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - 12 VAC 30-135 DMAS, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - 12 VAC 30-141 DMAS, 2004-2005 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - 12 VAC 35-105 DMHMRSAS, 2003-2005 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - 12 VAC 35-115 DMHMRSAS, 2002-2005 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - 12 VAC 35-155 DMHMRSAS, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - 12 VAC 35-180 DMHMRSAS, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - 12 VAC 35-210 DMHMRSAS, 2004-2005 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Special Report DMHMRSAS, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - 18 VAC 16-20 DHP, 2003-2005 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - 18 VAC 16-20 -10 DHP, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - 18 VAC 65-20 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - 18 VAC 65-40 DHP, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - 18 VAC 75-40 DHP, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - 18 VAC 76-30 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - 18 VAC 76-40 DHP, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - 18 VAC 85 DHP, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - 18 VAC 85-15 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - 18 VAC 85-20 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - 18 VAC 85-40 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - 18 VAC 85-50 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - 18 VAC 85-80 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - 18 VAC 85-101 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - 18 VAC 85-110 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - 18 VAC 85-120 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - 18 VAC 85-130 DHP, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - 18 VAC 90-15 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - 18 VAC 90-20 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - 18 VAC 90-20-10 DHP, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - 18 VAC 90-25 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - 18 VAC 90-25-10 DHP, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - 18 VAC 90-30 DHP, 2002-2005 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - 18 VAC 90-60 DHP, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - 18 VAC 95-20 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - 18 VAC 95-30 DHP, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - 18 VAC 105-20 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - 18 VAC 110-20 DHP, 2003-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - 18 VAC 110-20 DHP, 2003-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - 18 VAC 110-30 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - 18 VAC 110-20 DHP, 2003-2005 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - 18 VAC 115-15 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - 18 VAC 115-20 DHP, 2003-2005 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - 18 VAC 115-60 DHP, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - 18 VAC 125-15 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - 18 VAC 140-20 DHP, 2002-2005 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - 18 VAC 150-20 DHP, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - 22 VAC 15-10 DSS, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - 22 VAC 15-20 DSS, 2003-2004 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - 22 VAC 15-30 DSS, 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - 22 VAC 15-30 DSS, 2004-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - 22 VAC 15-20 DSS, 2002-2004 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - 22 VAC 30-10 DRS, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - 22 VAC 30-30 DRS, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - 22 VAC 40-20 DSS, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - 22 VAC 40-41 DSS, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - 22 VAC 40-71 DSS, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - 22 VAC 70-72 & 71 DSS, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - 22 VAC 40-80 DSS, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - 22 VAC 40-110 DSS, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - 22 VAC 40-111 DSS, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - 22 VAC 40-120 DSS, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - 22 VAC 40-130 DSS, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - 22 VAC 40-135 DSS, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - 22 VAC 40-141 DSS, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - 22 VAC 40-170 DSS, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - 22 VAC 40-180 DSS, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - 22 VAC 40-191 DSS, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - 22 VAC 40-200, 210, 240, 250, 260, 280, 800 DSS, 2003-2004 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - 22 VAC 40-211 DSS, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - 22 VAC 40-675 DSS, 2002-2005 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - 22 VAC 40-221 DSS, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - 22 VAC 40-250 DSS, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - 22 VAC 40-260 DSS, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - 22 VAC 40-293 DSS, 2003-2004 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - 22 VAC 40-295 DSS, 2003-2004 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - 22 VAC 40-325 DSS, 2003-2004 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - 22 VAC 40-375 DSS, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - 22 VAC 40-601 DSS, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - 22 VAC 40-660 DSS, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - 22 VAC 40-705 DSS, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - 22 VAC 40-740 DSS, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - 22 VAC 40-745 DSS, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - 22 VAC 40-770 DSS, 2004-2005 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - 22 VAC 40-880 DSS, 2004-2005 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - 22 VAC 40-901 DSS, 2004-2005 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - 22 VAC 42-11 DSS, 2004-2005 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - 22 VAC 140-20 DSS, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - 22 VAC 5-30 VDA, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - 12 VAC 5-30 VDA, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - 12 VAC 5-60 VDH, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - 12 VAC 5-70 & 71 VDH, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - 12 VAC 5-90 VDH, 2003-2005 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - 12 VAC 5-125 VDH, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - 12 VAC 5-190 & 191 VDH, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - 12 VAC 5-200 VDH, 2003-2004 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - 12 VAC 5-218 VDH, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - 12 VAC 5-230 VDH, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - 2002 HB 5 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - 2002 HB 8 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - 2002 HB 9 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - 2002 HB 10 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - 2002 HB 25 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - 2002 HB 37 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Legislative Studies, 1999-2004 [bulk 2002-2003]
  - ACF Contacts on Welfare Reform TANF Reauthorization, undated (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Aging, 2002-2003 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Balancing the TANF Budget (FY 05/06), 2003-2004 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Child Care Funding, 2002-2004 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Contacts on Welfare Reform - TANF II, 1999-2003 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Social Services, 2002-2003 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Social Services IV-E/Revenue Maximization, 2000-2002 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Social Services Reorganization, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Federal TANF Reauthorization, 2002-2003 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Health, 2000-2004, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Health, 2000-2004, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Health, 2000-2004, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Health, 2000-2004, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Heinz Family Philanthropies Prescription Drug Study (Item 298-E), 1999-2003 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - HJR 122 - Examination of the Prevalence of Methylphenidate and Amphetamine Prescriptions in the Commonwealth, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - HJR 199 - Requests to Develop a Joint / Cooperative Methodology / Singular Licensing Entity for Residential Services for Individuals with Mental Disabilties or Substance Abuse Problems, undated (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Studies - DSS, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Studies - OIG, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Local Consolidation Studies, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Medical Assistance Services, 2002-2003, fo. 1 of 5 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Medical Assistance Services, 2002-2003, fo. 2 of 5 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Medical Assistance Services, 2002-2003, fo. 3 of 5 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Medical Assistance Services, 2002-2003, fo. 4 of 5 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Medical Assistance Services, 2002-2003, fo. 5 of 5 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Mental Health, 2002-2003, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Mental Health, 2002-2003, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - OCS, 2002 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Planning for State TANF plan, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Responses to NCSL/NGS on Welfare Reform, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Responses to TANF Advisory Group, 2002-2003 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Secure Virginia: Panel Recommendations, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Social Services, 2002-2003 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Social Services, 2002 Sept - Dec, 2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Social Services, 2002 Sept - Dec, 2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Social Services, 2002-2004, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Social Services, 2002-2004, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Social Services, 2002-2004, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Studies Generally, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Study: Commission on Prescription Drug Assistance (HJR 90 2002), 2002 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Study: Guardianship Assessment (301 C2), 2002 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Study: Office of the Inspector General (298C 2002), 2002 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Study: Therapeutic Interchange of Chemically Dissimilar Drugs (SJR 197), 2000 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - Study: Treatment Options for Offenders with MH/SA (SJ97/HJ142), 2002 (Box 132, Folder 24)
  - TANF II Advisory Committee Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 132, Folder 25)
  - TANF Spending Plan 03/04, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 26)
  - Utilization and Costs of Pharmaceuticals in Government-Funded Healthcare Programs - Item 2985, 2000-2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 132, Folder 27)
  - Utilization and Costs of Pharmaceuticals in Government-Funded Healthcare Programs - Item 2985, 2000-2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 132, Folder 28)
  - Welfare Reform, 1999-2001 (Box 132, Folder 29)
- Series VII: Special Assistant Files, 2002-2005
  - 2005 Legislative Process - Preparation, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Agency Talking Points, 2005 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Aging Task Force Meetings, 2004, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Aging Task Force Meetings, 2004, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Cheat Sheet Development, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Cheat Sheets (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Code / Resolutions / General Assembly (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Assisted Living: Communication / Public Awareness, 1999-2005 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Final Recommendation Work-out, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Assisted Living Facilities HJR 199, undated (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Legislation Development, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Assisted Living Meeting Summaries, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Assisted Living Facilities October, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Presentations, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Regulation Development, 2005 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Research, Other States, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Uniform Assessment Instrument, 2004-2005 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Assisted Living Facilities Uniform Assessment Instrument, 2005 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Bill Assignments, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Calendars, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Calendars, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Carried Over Information (Legislation), 2004 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Children: Head Start / Pre-K (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Comparison of House and Senate Budget Agreements, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Affairs, 2002 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Continued Legislation from the 2004 Session, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Health - Legislation, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Email, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - REVIEW: Familiarization Workshop, 2002 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Gary Janak Project, undated (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly 2005 Summary Sheets, 2004-2005 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Governor Amendment - 2005 General Assembly Talking Points, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Governor Letter Requests, undated (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Grant Application, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Healthy Aging Meeting Notes, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Highlights and Accomplishments, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Hofheimer Nusbaum, P.C., 2003 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Important Numbers (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Kudos, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Language Meeting Documents, 2005 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Meetings, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Work in Progress, 2004-2005 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Long Term Care - Question and Answer, 2005 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Long Term Care - Workshops, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Long-Term Care Awareness: Media, 2003 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Long-Term Care: Correspondence, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Long-Term Care: Mailings / Resource List, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Long-Term Care: Media / Press Conference, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Long-Term Care: Meeting Summaries, 2004 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Long-Term Care: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - Long-Term Care: Project Background, 2004-2005 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Media Issues OSHHR, undated (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous - Legislative, 2002 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 [1] (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 [2] (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - No Wrong Door, 2005 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Notebooks, 2004 and undated (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Olmstead (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - OSHHR Info, undated (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Patrons, 2005 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Prisoner / Re-entry, 2004-2005 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Proposals, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Protocol, 2002 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Research / Examples, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Resources, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Reviewed, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - REVIEW: Secure Virginia Panel, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Studies, 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Studies, 2004-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Sunset Provisions, 2004-2005 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Regulatory Town Hall - Users' Manual for Secretariat and Governor's Office Staff, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 20)
- Series VIII: Special Projects, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
  - 1998-2001 Locality Expo/Census Info., undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - 2005 Legislative Session, 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - 2005 Legislative Session, 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - 2005 Legislative Session, 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - 2006 Budget Preparation, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - 4th Annual Critical Issues Symposium - Virginia Coalition of Private Provider Associations, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Council on the Future of Nursing, 2002 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Agencies Serving Virginians with Disabilities: Report on Audit for the Year Ended June 30, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Agency Budget Request Brief Summary Forms for 2005, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Agency Legislation - 2004 Session, 2003, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Agency Legislation - 2004 Session, 2003, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Agency Legislation - 2004 Session, 2003, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Agency Legislation - 2004 Session, 2003, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Agency Summaries, undated (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - An Appropriation Act Prescribed Study of the Comprehensive Services Act, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Application for the FFY 2005 SAPT Block Grant Funds, 2004, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Application for the FFY 2005 SAPT Block Grant Funds, 2004, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Application for the FFY 2005 SAPT Block Grant Funds, 2004, fo. 3 fo 3 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Assisted Living Facilities - Bills, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Assistive Technology Loan Fund Authority Financial Statements Year Ended June 30, 2003, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Beth Shalom Home of Eastern Virginia, 2005 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Biennial Report: Virginia's Disability Services System: Interim Report, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Blue Ribbon Plan to Prevent Child Abuse and Neglect in Virginia, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Bright Futures: Guidelines for Health Supervision of Infants, Children, and Adolescents, 2nd Edition Revised - Pocket Guide, undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Budget Bill, 2004-2006 Bienium, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Budget Bill, 2006-2006 Bienium, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Budget Correspondence 2005 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Budget Documentation, 2004, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Budget Documentation, 2004, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Budget Documentation, 2004, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Budget Documentation, 2004, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Budget Documents and Notes, 2005, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Budget Documents and Notes, 2005, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Budget Documents and Notes, 2005, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Budget Documents and Notes, 2005, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Budget Documents, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Budget Documents, 2005, fo. 1 of 5 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Budget Documents, 2005, fo. 2 of 5 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Budget Documents, 2005, fo. 3 of 5 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Budget Documents, 2005, fo. 4 of 5 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Budget Documents, 2005, fo. 5 of 5 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Budget Materials, 2004, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Budget Materials, 2004, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Budget Materials, 2005, fo.1 of 2 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Budget Materials, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Building a Prototype National Health Information Network in Appalachia, 2005 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Business Process Reengineering: Virginia Social Services System, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Capital Fund Priorities: Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Capital Fund Priority Listing: Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Caregiver Proposal: Volunteer Caregiver Awards Program, 2005 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Child Advocacy Center Funding, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Child Advocacy Centers, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Child Advocacy Centers, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Child and Family Services Federal Review, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Child and Family Services Review: Statewide Assessment, 2003 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Child Maltreatment 2003 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Children's Health System, 2004 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Committee Studying Treatment options for offenders with mental illness or substance abuse disorders (SJR 97/HJR 142), 2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Committee Studying Treatment options for offenders with mental illness or substance abuse disorders (SJR 97/HJR 142), 2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Committee Studying Treatment Options for Offenders with Mental Illness or Substance Abuse Disorders, 2002 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Community Support Services Trainer Program: The Universe Between Our Ears, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Comparison of House and Senate Budget Amendments: House Bill 1500 and Senate Bill 700, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Agreement between DMHMRSAS and GD Williamsburg, LLC for the replacement of the Hancock Geriatric Center, Eastern State Hospital, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Comprehensive Agreement between DMHMRSAS and GD Williamsburg, LLC for the replacement of the Hancock Geriatric Center, Eastern State Hospital, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Comprehensive Agreement between DMHMRSAS and GS Williamsburg, LLC for the Virginia Center for Behavioral Rehabilitation, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Comprehensive Agreement between DMHMRSAS and GS Williamsburg, LLC for the Virginia Center for Behavioral Rehabilitation, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Comprehensive Services Act for At Risk Youth and Families: State Executive Council, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Services Act for At-Risk Youth - Portsmouth, 2001-2002 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Services Act State and Local Advisory Team, 2004 (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Comprehensive Services Act, 2004 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Services Act, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Conceptual Stage (Part 1) Submission Under the Public/Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act of 2002 ... Project: Hancock Geriatric Treatment Center, 2004-2005 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2005 [1], fo. 1 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2005 [1], fo. 2 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2005 [1], fo. 3 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 2005 [1], fo. 4 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 1 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 2 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 3 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 4 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 5 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 6 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 7 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - REVIEW: Constitutent Correspondence, 2005, fo. 8 of 8 (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 [1] (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 [2], fo. 1 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 [2], fo. 2 of 2 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 [3], fo. 1 of 4 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 [3], fo. 2 of 4 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 [3], fo. 3 of 4 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 [3], fo. 4 of 4 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [1], fo. 1 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [1], fo. 2 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [1], fo. 3 of 3 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 1 of 6 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 2 of 6 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 3 of 6 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 4 of 6 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 5 of 6 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 [2], fo. 6 of 6 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, December 2004 - August 2005, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 2004 - August 2005, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, December 2004 - August 2005, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, December 2004 - August 2005, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - REVIEW: Correspondence, 2005 [1] (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - REVIEW: Correspondence, 2005 [2] (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 2005 [3], fo. 1 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2005, [3] fo. 2 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2005 [3], fo. 3 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2005 [3], fo. 4 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 5 January 2006 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Notes and Reports, 2005-2006, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Notes and Reports, 2005-2006, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Presentations and Meeting Materials, 2003-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Presentations and Meeting Materials, 2003-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - REVIEW: Correspondence, Presentations and Meeting Materials, 2003-2005 (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Presentations, Reports and Other Materials, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Presentations, Reports and Other Materials, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Dept. of Aging, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Foster Care - Proposed Regulations, undated (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Interagency Civil Admissions Advisory Council, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Meth Watch, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Olmstead Initiative, November 2004 - March 2005 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 10)